Within the Clover's fifth leaf, there lives a devil.
Asta, born unable to harness mana, was granted the power of anti-magic from his five-leaf grimoire,
giving him the ability to nullify spells.
Unfortunately, the members of Spade Kingdom's Dark Triad also possessed powers from the devils of the Underworld,
and used them to launch an invasion on the neighboring countries.
Gaining strength from his belief in himself and from the support of his friends,
Asta continues to fight for the safety of this world.
Asta and the others took over the town of Tola, one of Spade's bases, and returned to the Heart Kingdom.
However, they weren't able to rest for long.
Charmy's power and appetite had increased during her training,
and, along with a group of various wild animals,
she came close to devouring all of the food in the forest.
Picture magic! Invasion of Heat and Fused Ice!
Peace was briefly restored.
Meanwhile, Yuno returned to his home village of Hajj after receiving a strange message,
and heard some unexpected news from the man he met there.
You belong to the house of Grinverial.
It's Sion, the Prince of the Spade Kingdom.
We're gonna wake you in for the brand new world.
Yeah!
We're gonna take you to the brand new world.
To the brand new world!
We're gonna wake you in for the brand new world.
Get your hands up, baby!
We're gonna take you to the brand new world.
Yeah!
They drowned out!
Get it on! Get it on! 始めよう!
難航不楽のリアリティ!
立ち止まる時間はないさ!
Hold on! Hold on!
Yeah!
Now this time, fight for liberty!
真実性!
飲み込み常識!
覚え!
欲求の先にある朝!
Oh, yeah!
傾向に埋もらった人生の夢!
Hands up!
Shout it! Shout it! Louder!
Yes! Do it! Do it! Start it!
Never give up!
限界を超えてもかすくして!
Experience!
We can't face!
Let's go!
Living myself!
衝動的に突き進め!
Don't be afraid!
誰よりも高く飛べ!
Take it to the sky!
想像を超えた世界をこの手に!
The ground up!
想像せよ!
偽りのない自然の道!
Yes!
It's a ground up!
Hey, yeah!
Believe in myself!
Believe in yourself!
Hey, yeah!
Yeah!
It's now time!
The magic he has!
It's hard to believe that he comes from the Forsaken Realm!
Who cares where he's from?
What matters is that Yuno's an extremely talented magic knight!
Uh-oh!
So that's how it is, huh?
Sorry?
You'd better get in line!
What?
Yuno has insane fan clubs all over the kingdom, just so you know!
Hey, shut up!
It isn't like that!
He is amazing, though!
If he made VC in just a year and a half,
then I'm sure he'll end up becoming the wizard king one day!
Hmm.
Yuno is what?!
He's the prince of the Spain kingdom?!
I mean, I knew he was special, but the boy was actually royalty all alone?!
This is incredible!
It's a little surprising, but I did always have a sneaking suspicion deep down!
Yuno Prince Charming!
You're so loud!
So that's where that elegant, sophisticated air comes from!
What is this creature?
I am the wind spirit Silph, one of the far great spirits!
Oh!
And I'm closer to Yuno than anyone else is!
So you control the wind spirit?
You're amazing, Prince Yuno!
Hmm.
Wait a minute!
Then what does this make Asta?
Who's Asta?
The other child who was left here at the same time!
They were side by side!
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm not familiar.
All I know is that you are Prince Yuno of the Spade Kingdom.
Hmm.
Hold on.
This is going too fast.
You're saying I'm some kind of Prince?
Yes.
If I was someone that important,
then why was I abandoned at a church in the Clover Kingdom?
Well, you see…
Let me change the question.
Who are you and why are you here?
Right.
I should have said, my name is Ralph,
and my purpose here is to tell you the truth about who you are.
I traveled through the strong magic region,
carrying the thoughts and mana of my brethren with me,
just as my father did.
Here.
Flame Magic Trace Mirage.
Once you see this, you'll understand.
Where am I?
They say on that day,
a beam of light cut through the clouds
that hovered above the Spade Kingdom.
It seemed like a sign that a brighter future
was just over the horizon.
My king…
Hmm?
Worrying won't do any good, sir.
You're right.
The child has arrived!
He's a healthy baby boy.
I'm so grateful you've come into my life.
My beautiful son.
Sial…
My love…
I know you're exhausted.
Darling…
I obtained this magic stone long ago,
when I was traveling through the strong magic region.
It'll protect Yuno…
Is that his name, then?
Is that his name?
I know if it's not alive.
I'm so grateful you've come into my life.
My beautiful son.
My beautiful son…
Sial…
My love…
I know you're exhausted.
Darling…
you're exhausted darling i obtained this magic stone long ago when i was traveling through the
strong magic region it'll protect you know is that his name then you know if it's a boy
i believe that's what you said yes
he's here the prince is born our kingdom now has an heir the prince of the speed kingdom is born at
last the festivities carried on well into the night your birth was truly a ray of hope that
warmed the bitter cold winter that had isolated our land for so long
everyone always smiled whenever they were in your presence
easy there how do i calm him down the first division captain of the mage defense force can't
handle a kid huh did you forget what you learned from raising your own son or what
well for the most part my wife handled this sort of thing
is
hey i got him to stop crying king lois and queen cl wow talk about a great legacy
yeah this kid's gonna be a way stronger mage than you are in no time hey you watch your mouth
prince you know really is a sweet child
things are peaceful for now and it's our job to ensure that continues my son one day you'll join the
mage defense force and protect prince yuno with your very life yes father
he stopped crying yes do you think he's going to be all right huh well he's very sensitive someday
he'll need to be strong enough to take my place as the ruler of this kingdom
what's wrong he's just an infant darling isn't it a little early to concern ourselves with things
like that you think so it's much too soon right crybaby those were such happy times
none of us could have predicted they were about to come to a sudden end
the zogratus siblings have returned your subjugation mission was a success
now please take some time to recover we need you at your best to maintain peace in the spade kingdom
for peace yes of course as you wish sire
those three siblings keep a close eye on them but why do you say that father i have a bad feeling
louise darling did those three kill that group of rebels yes were they acting on orders from you
don't be absurd
there there it's all right for some reason i just don't trust them
i wonder why father said that all i know is nothing will shake my loyalty to this land
hey ralph you're ready to take a break yeah might as well thanks buddy
those three turned out to be the dark triad
if i had listened to my father's words we may have been able to avoid that terrible tragedy
i don't believe it
they're wiping out the entire mage defense force we can't stop them they're too strong
it was true all along those three have been bestowed with the power of the underworld
dante how could you
father where are the king and queen
are they the kingdom's future was left with me they're all just so weak it's kind of boring
honestly then i'll buy you some time hurry don't you think so i suppose thank you i swore i'd protect
him with my life make sure you survive
i will father
that night was the last time i ever saw him
is the prince all right yes he's not safe here if they found him they most likely wouldn't kill him but
they'll kidnap him for sure exactly they have no right to the throne so they'll try to take him alive
what makes you think it's the throne those villains are after
what else could it be couldn't say but i sense that their intentions are deeply sinister
we can't let them have prince yuno the zo gratis siblings know all of this kingdom's secrets just
as we do we must leave now do as we discussed they've gone in three separate directions
uh don't cry everything's all right after all i swore in my life that i'd always keep you safe
and i'm sure that stone will help protect you as well
the strong magic region there's no way he'll make it
what should we do sir doesn't matter but if the prince lives we'll have a problem won't we
if that concerns you then kill him right
i will protect you whatever it takes
prince you know
that's a church you'll be safe there this will be my final spell for you my prince
now live and be strong
that was fast
i led them far away from the church they shouldn't be able to find him now
stay safe prince you know i refuse to be killed by you
ralph
the future is in your hands
i know
considering the massive amount of mana you have i assume you're able to see that everything i showed you
actually happened there were no lies in any part of it yeah well that's exactly what a liar would say
don't believe this creep you know my family served the house of grin burial for generations
it's not just me you have countless subjects praying for your safety your highness
and they're in grave danger
what's wrong there's trouble sir the headquarters is under attack
please help us please help us oh no
we're allowed to have as much fun as we want
right lord xenon as long as you leave the arcane stage magic night alive
please wait sir if they were able to enter the clover kingdom that easily
they must be the dark triad or someone just as strong you can't be rash
sorry but i am the vice captain of the golden dawn
prince yuno i'll go too i will no you need to stay in bed
you know let me guess you look scary because you're thinking about all the different ways you're
gonna punish the bad guys i'm right aren't i i'm so smart you belong to the house of grin burial
it's sion the prince of the spade kingdom even so i am also yuno of the clover kingdom
i need to get there faster
from the looks of them they're spade kingdom mages i don't know how they got here but they must be
tough if they made it into our headquarters teach them a lesson go blast them with your attack spells
what what the what the they're not hurt but where'd the other one go
come on is that the best you can do but i heard you guys were supposed to be the toughest squad in the
clover kingdom well guess i can't blame you only a select few were good enough to get powers from
the dark triad and we were at the top of the list we're the dark disciples all of us are stage zero mages
stage zero no way
he's gone
hey stone magic just like me
too bad you're such a weakling
sharon
when you've got a devil's power it takes your magic to a new level
our army captains can do about five percent but i'm strong enough to unleash closer to 40
and since lord xenon's possessed
he's got upwards of 80. so here you are
you're captain vengeance of the golden dawn we hear you're one of the few magic knights whose power
has reached the arcane stage this mama
stop get away from lord vengeance right now stand down alakdora they're too powerful
last time i allowed myself to become possessed but this is my chance to stand up and fight for my captain
they will kill you that's a magic knight of golden dawn
i will strike you down
what did he do
world tree magic magic warning ash
lord vengeance thank you devil possessed or not you'll pay dearly for causing harm to my
subordinates so that's world tree magic is it
our side could certainly use that i'll be taking you with me oh magic eternal fangs
i'm here
someone else joining the fun sorry buddy you're late to the party
what the hell do you think you're doing
you're my comrades
so
mother
me
Ima tobi-ta-te
Ano una-bara o mi-o-to-site
Dare-yori mo to-oku
Nando-demo will fly
Beautiful
Do-na keshiki mo
Kimi to i-reba kagaya-ku-yo
Da-kara zu-to soba-ni-i-te
And never let go
Bopo no kono te-o
Hanasanai-de doko ma-demo
Tzite-kite-hoshii
The world is so beautiful
Who cares where he's from?
What matters is that Yuno's an extremely talented magic knight
Uh-oh, so that's how it is, huh?
Sorry?
You'd better get in line
What?
Yuno has insane fan clubs all over the kingdom, just so you know
Duh, of course I know about the fan clubs
Who do you think is the president of the Golden Dawn chapter?
There's a Golden Dawn chapter?!
You said yourself they're all over the kingdom
And this is the squad Yuno's in
So why wouldn't we have one?
Right
I have buttons, folders, acrylic statues
Every single piece of Yuno merchandise that exists!
And of course I follow his social media
Wait, really?
You mean...
Yuno's on the internet?!
You monster
I won't let you do this to my squad mates
Black Clover, page 161
Xenon's power
Whether you have the strength of a devil or not
Mark my words, I WILL DEFEAT
All four
I know
I'm sorry, one of the two WOOD's podcasts, I like that
SON
My name is Oν
My 2
Moon
We areening what this ketmine